<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<index>
  <path src="../hubfs/gallery"/>

  <album title="The Classic Cardovan" id="kitchen1">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This refaced kitchen features Cordovan on Cherry with a Sabel Glaze. This classically rich cabinet color is highlighted with custom Classic Raised Panel style #10875. Countertop was supplied by the customer. ]]>
    </description>
    <image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Breckenridge Light" id="kitchen2">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This refaced kitchen features Antique White cabinets with a Walnut Glaze. This popular color is highlighted by the simple, yet elegant Breckenridge Square door style. Countertop supplied by customer. ]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Classic Cherry Tea" id="kitchen3">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[These Classic Cherry cabinets are made unique with a rich Black Glaze. The Vintage Raised Panel style brings decorative appeal to the Silestone Quartz countertops in Tea Leaf.]]>
    </description>
    <image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Canterbury Square" id="kitchen4">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[Antique White cabinets with a Walnut Glaze in Breckenridge Square style perfectly pair with the neutral variants in the Cambria Quartz countertop in Canterbury. The Corian backsplash in Sandalwood with an Offset Diamond pattern is both beautiful and durable. ]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="The White Walnut" id="kitchen5">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This traditional kitchen features the popular Antique White cabinet door color with a Walnut Glaze in Stonebridge style. The countertops are Granite certified by Kitchen Magic.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Maple Milan" id="kitchen6">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[These Hard Maple cabinets feature custom color #1767 and the Italian inspired Milan style. The subtle colors in the cabinets highlight the Silestone Quartz countertop in Santa Cecelia with a Hanover edge.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
  </album>

    <album title="Black Cherry Island" id="kitchen7">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This beautifully refaced kitchen features classic Washington Cherry cabinets with a rich Black Glaze in a Classic Raised Panel style #10875. Countertop supplied by customer.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="The Cherry Sable Capri" id="kitchen8">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This simple, yet classic kitchen features Cordovan Cherry cabinets with a Sabel Glaze in Classic Raised Panel style #30 and #10. The light color of the Silestone Quartz Countertop in Capri Limestone brings contrast to the kitchen.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Cherry Uba Tuba" id="kitchen9">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[Cordovan on Cherry cabinetry graced with sabel glaze on a classic raised panel door. The counters are furnished with luxurious Uba Tuba granite.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen7.jpg"/>		
  </album>

  <album title="Maples of Winter Island" id="kitchen10">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This light and airy kitchen features Hard Maple cabinets with a Natural glaze in Classic Raised Panel style #10. The durable and maintenance-free countertop is Corian Solid Surface in Tumbleweed with an Eased edge. The island brings contrast to the room Winter White cabinets with a Walnut Glaze in Stonebridge and a Zodiaq Quartz countertop in Smokey Topaz.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Cordovan Cherry Greens" id="kitchen11">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This kitchen bridges traditional and contemporary design with Cordovan Cherry cabinets in Classic Raised Panel style #10 and Granite certified by Kitchen Magic countertops in Tunis Green/Verde Peacock. The custom hutch features Granite countertops in Eucalyptus Green.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>	
  </album>

  <album title="Prestigious Dunewood Square" id="kitchen12">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[Neutral kitchens never go out of style, which led this homeowner to choose Dunewood cabinets in Prestige Square style, which contrast perfectly with the Zodiaq Quartz countertop in Mystic Black with a Roundover edge.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Maple White Galaxy" id="kitchen13">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[The Maple cabinets in Alpine White with Classic Raised Panel style #10 give this kitchen a clean look. The Zodiaq Quartz countertops in Mystic Black with a Roundover edge bring dramatic contrast to the space.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen7.jpg"/>		
  </album>

  <album title="Warm Winter in Stonebridge" id="kitchen14">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This kitchen uses warm and cool tones bring a unique style to the space, featuring Winter White cabinets with a Walnut Glaze in Stonebridge style and Granite certified by Kitchen Magic countertops in Juparana Crema Bordeaux with a Roundover edge.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Secret Maple Harvest" id="kitchen15">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This Fall inspiration features Maple cabinets with custom color #1737 and President Raised Panel style #M30. The countertop is Granite certified by Kitchen Magic in Autumn Wheat.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
  </album>

    <album title="Lancaster Raised Cherry" id="kitchen16">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[These Classic Cherry cabinets with Vintage Raised Panel style highlight the golden variants in the Cambria Quartz countertop in Lancaster with a Roundover edge.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Maple Harvest Gold" id="kitchen17">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[The custom wood cabinets are made from Hard Maple in Harvest Gold with a Pewter Glaze in the simple Square style. The countertops are durable Corian Solid Surface in Rain Cloud with an Eased edge.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Hazelnut Mountain Mist" id="kitchen18">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This refaced kitchen features Hazelnut cabinets with Vintage Raised Panel style and Silestone Quartz countertops in Mountain Mist with a Bevel Edge. ]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
  </album>

    <album title="White Walnut Island in Cordovan" id="kitchen19">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This classical design features Cordovan Cherry cabinets with Classic Raised Panel style #10875 and Granite certified by Kitchen Magic countertops in Galaxy Black with a Bevel edge. The island helps break up the visible space by offering the contrasting colors of Antique White cabinets with a Walnut glaze in Breckenridge style and Granite countertops in New Venecian Gold.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="The Cordovan Crown" id="kitchen20">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This kitchen highlights regal inspirations with Cordovan Cherry cabinets in Classic Raised Panel Style #10875. The Rope crown moulding adds sophistication and added aesthetic appeal. Countertop supplied by customer. ]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Maple, Pewter and Pepper" id="kitchen21">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[The Maple Harvest Gold cabinets with a Pewter Glaze bring warmth to this traditional kitchen. The traditional design is continued through the cabinets in Mitered Classic Raised Panel style #10875 and the Corian countertop in Pepper Ivory.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="The Euro" id="kitchen22">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This kitchen features contemporary European design schemes with Hardrock Maple cabinets in Euro Plain style. Countertop supplied by customer.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Custom Glass and Green" id="kitchen23">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[Exclusive styles are brought forth through the custom-colored cabinets in Classic Raised Panel style #10875. The kitchen is given a unique edge with Zodiaq Quartz countertops in Argo Green with a Roudover edge.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Hard Maple Island" id="kitchen24">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[The traditional details in this kitchen are highlighted by the Hard Maple Autumn cabinets with a Maple-White glaze. For a custom look, the homeowner chose different styles for the upper and lower cabinets--#90209 for the upper, and #10209 for the lower. Countertop supplied by customer.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
  </album>

    <album title="Maple Caramel Espresso" id="kitchen25">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This small kitchen is designed to look larger with Hard Maple cabinets with a Natural Finish and Caramel Glaze. The Miter style in Classic Raised Panel style #10827 adds grandeur, while the floating shelves in Espresso make the kitchen appear more expansive by breaking up the space. The countertop is Cambria Quartz in Wellington.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen7.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen8.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen9.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen10.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen11.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen12.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen13.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="The Prestige Cathedral" id="kitchen26">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This commonly shaped kitchen features the warm tones of Cherry Pear cabinets and the prominent arches of Prestige Cathedral styled cabinets. The Silestone Quartz countertops in Black Canyon pair perfectly with neutral cabinets.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>	
  </album>

  <album title="Crowned Cordovan" id="kitchen27">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This classic kitchen has glamorous style thanks to the Cordovan on Cherry cabinets with Classic Raised Panel style #10875, and Granite Certified by Kitchen Magic in New Venecian Gold. The backsplash features maintenance-free Solid Surface Meganite in Canvas Mist.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen7.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen8.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen9.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen10.jpg"/>		
  </album>

  <album title="The Frosty White" id="kitchen28">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This designer favorite features Hard Maple cabinets with a Frosty White colourtone and Madison style. The simple white cabinets are contrasted with the dark Cambria countertops in Edinborough.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Maple Espresso Gold" id="kitchen29">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This contemporary kitchen design features Hard Maple cabinets in Espresso with Classic Raised Panel style #10. The countertops are Granite certified by Kitchen Magic in New Venecian Gold.
]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>	
  </album>

  <album title="The Antique Statesman" id="kitchen30">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This colorful kitchen features Antique White cabinets with Statesman style. The island also features Statesman style cabinets in Chocolate Pear. These simple elements are highlighted by the dark Cambria Quartz countertop in Oakhampton.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen7.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen8.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen9.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Maple Harvest Glaze" id="kitchen31">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[Description coming soon.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Ginger Cherry Gold" id="kitchen32">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This kitchen features Ginger on Cherry enhanced with Classic Raised Panel doors. The Vyana Gold Granite counters and backsplash top off this bright and cheery design.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen7.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Vintage Hazelnut" id="kitchen33">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[Hazelnut Custom Cabinetry adorns this new kitchen redesign complete with our popular Vintage Raised Panel doors. The beautiful quartz countertops are none other than Canterbury by Cambria.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>	
  </album>

    <album title="Black and White Chocolate" id="kitchen34">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[Antique White cabinets in our Manchester style beautifully contrasts the Chololate Pear island dressed up Prestige Kershaw style. The Black Galaxy countertops complete this simple, yet elegent design.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
  </album>

  <album title="Black Cherry Canterbury" id="kitchen35">
    <description>
      <![CDATA[This all new kitchen is designed with Classic Cherry maintenance-free cabinets, accented with Black Glaze in popular Vintage Raised Panel style. The luxury quartz countertop is made by Cambria. The selection is Canterbury.]]>
    </description>
	<image filename="kitchen1.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen2.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen3.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen4.jpg"/>
	<image filename="kitchen5.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen6.jpg"/>
    <image filename="kitchen7.jpg"/>		
  </album>

    
</index>